{
    "id": "456e5560714a4e45992f3e7cab1b18f9",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is intelligent ………………… hard working.",
            "description": "Either as well as or and can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "as well",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7be457a2fd749b28ea78057f4ace0e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. the girl tried her best, she could not get the first rank.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "871d8ac85e0f49d3b5a022688d8a4529"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he is not educated, he has great practical wisdom.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63004060a17d473d87dd11ee573f9d4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctors treated her well …………………… they could not save her.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "however",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a759060d45f64b17821e96c9e3a260dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother as well as her children …………………… waiting there.",
            "description": "When you connect a singular and a plural verb with as well as, the verb agrees with the first noun.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3690ad7d070549829f86457713bb8bab"
        },
        {
            "question": "He treated me …………………….. I was a stranger to him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as if",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d3e7cee21f046ae92a7ba13b15f0f90"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. it was raining, he opened the umbrella.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35a04ce11def48ea98a0dd912eb4cfd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. the servant was honest, his master trusted him.",
            "description": "All of these words can indicate the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "Because",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a6c99697559240c096a71bd3d6c3d866"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hall is not …………………… to accommodate all the students.",
            "description": "When enough is an adverb modifying an adjective or adverb, it goes after the adjective/adverb modified it. ",
            "answers": [
                "too big",
                "enough big",
                "big enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "80e838af2ae3489e9d860cdbe21d93b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………….. proud to beg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab59a0f03afa43d3a1f1a7bf2db69ea3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He borrowed some money from his friends ……………………. he could buy a car.",
            "description": "So that indicates purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "so as to",
                "in order to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e22e09581b294dd186d78f70b9a4e9c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He offered his daughter a prize, so that she ……………………. work hard.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the past tense, the verb in the subordinate clause will also be in the past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47ae46471e514300ae038992d643da71"
        }
    ]
}